Guide to the Office of Cooperative Research, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Office of Cooperative Research, Yale University, records
1902-2004
RU 892
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
26.5
The records consist of contracts, agreements, and acknowledgments maintained by the Office of Cooperative Research at Yale. The records document patents and licensing of patents with organizations outside of Yale.
Yale University. Office of Cooperative Research
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 5-D (YRG 5-D), Investment and insurance records of Yale University.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of contracts, agreements, and acknowledgments maintained by the Office of Cooperative Research at Yale. The records document patents and licensing of patents with organizations outside of Yale.
Patents; Yale University. Office of Cooperative Research
- Patent records and license agreements, circa 1902-1998; Accession 2002-A-089
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until January 1, 2033
- Patents, license agreements, assignments, material transfer agreements, confidential enclosure agreements and research agreements, circa 1984-2002; Accession 2003-A-015
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2037
  - 1201 Confidential Disclosure Agreement (Hamilton) (Box 1)
  - 1201 Confidential Disclosure Agreement (Hamilton) (Box 1)
  - 1200 Confidential Disclosure Agreement \(Ghosh) (Box 1)
  - 1201 and 1225 Confidential Disclosure Agreement (Hamilton) 5/20/2002 (Box 2)
  - 190 Material Transfer Agreement (Grindley) 01/04/02 (Box 3)
  - 1200 Confidential Disclosure Agreement (Ghosh) 01/18/2002 (Box 3)
  - 190 Material Transfer Agreement (Grindley) 04/14/1998 (Box 4)
  - 1202 Confidential Disclosure Agreement (Kocsis) 08/07/01 (Box 4)
  - 1201 Confidential Disclosure Agreement (Hamilton) 11/28/01 (Box 4)
  - 1200 Confidential Disclosure Agreement (Ghosh and Trillium) 1/18/01 (Box 4)
  - 1201 Confidential Disclosure Agreement (Hamilton and Achillion) 07/17/02 (Box 4)
- Legal documents, patents, licenses, CDA, MTA, etc., 2001-2003; Accession 2003-A-102
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2038
  - 1201 Inter-Institutional Agreement (Hamilton and Univ of WA) 07/11/2002 (Box 1)
  - 1201 Material Transfer Agreement (Hamilton) between Yale and Achillion, 10/17/2002 (Box 1)
  - 1321 (Box 1)
- Patent records, circa 1989-1990; Accession 2004-A-082
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2025